Guide to the Communications Workers of America Records Addendum WAG.124.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Files of the Presidents Office, 1970-1998.
  - Subseries I:D: Joseph A. Beirne Foundation, Joseph A. Bierne and Ray Hackney Scholarship Funds, 1977-1998.
    - RHSF: United States Correspondence, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Alternates and Confirmations, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Recipients: Alvarez-Argentina, 1991-1994 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Recipients: Zunino-Argentina, 1991-1994 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Recipients: Hoyte-Barbados, 1991-1994 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Recipients: Ferreira-Brazil, 1991-1994 (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Recipients: Arias-Costa Rica, 1991-1994 (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Recipients: Rodriquez-Costa Rica, 1991-1994 (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Alternates and District Confirmations, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 20)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Recipients: Atkinson, Mona L., 1991 (Box 66, Folder 21)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Recipients: Costa, Mark W., 1991-1994 (Box 66, Folder 22)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Recipients: Jones, Carla L., 1991-1993 (Box 66, Folder 23)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Recipients: Key, Mari A., 1991-1994 (Box 66, Folder 24)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Recipients: Loegering, Jay J., 1991-1995 (Box 66, Folder 25)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Recipients: Sah, Alanna R., 1991-1995 (Box 66, Folder 26)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Recipients: Valentino, Patrick J., 1991-1995 (Box 66, Folder 27)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Recipients: Walker, Dana M., 1991-1994 (Box 66, Folder 28)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Recipients: Gonzalez-Argentina, 1992-1995 (Box 66, Folder 29)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Recipients: Canha-Brazil, 1992-1995 (Box 66, Folder 30)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Recipients: Gonzalez-Alvarez-Chile, 1992-1995 (Box 66, Folder 31)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Recipients: Arias-Costa Rica, 1992-1995 (Box 66, Folder 32)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Recipients: Alvarado-Martinez, 1992-1995 (Box 66, Folder 33)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Recipients: Gonzalez-Alvarez- Guatemala, 1992-1995 (Box 66, Folder 34)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Recipients: Galicia-Mush-Guatemala, 1992-1995 (Box 66, Folder 35)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Recipients: Carmelita de Bies-Surinam, 1992-1995 (Box 66, Folder 36)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Recipients: Baldwin, Tamara S., 1992-1995 (Box 66, Folder 37)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Recipients: Blackburn, Kimyon N., 1992-1995 (Box 66, Folder 38)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Recipients: Keenan, Megan M., 1992-1995 (Box 66, Folder 39)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Recipients: Lassek, Stephanie A., 1992-1995 (Box 66, Folder 40)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Recipients: Pluto, Jodelle M., 1992-1995 (Box 66, Folder 41)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Recipients: Slater, Rhonda L., 1992-1995 (Box 66, Folder 42)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Recipients: Thomas, Stephen W., 1992-1996 (Box 66, Folder 43)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Recipients: Townsend, Francis J., 1992-1995 (Box 66, Folder 44)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Alternates and Confirmations, 1993 (Box 66, Folder 45)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Recipients: Badino-Argentina, 1993-1996 (Box 66, Folder 46)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Recipients: Roberts-Barbados, 1993-1996 (Box 66, Folder 47)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Recipients: Simmons-Bermuda, 1993-1995 (Box 66, Folder 48)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Recipients: Vargas-Alvarado-Brazil, 1993-1996 (Box 66, Folder 49)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Recipients: Crespo de Olivera-Brazil, 1993-1996 (Box 66, Folder 50)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Recipients: Barboza-Silva-Brazil, 1993-1996 (Box 66, Folder 51)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Recipients: Ariastuk-Costa Rica, 1993-1996 (Box 66, Folder 52)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Recipients: Gutierrez-Costa Rica, 1993-1996 (Box 66, Folder 53)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Alternates and District Confirmations, 1993 (Box 66, Folder 54)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Recipients: Bennett, Monte J., 1993-1996 (Box 66, Folder 55)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Recipients: Brown, Philip W. Jr., 1993-1996 (Box 66, Folder 56)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Recipients: Hanson, Carrie L., 1993-1996 (Box 66, Folder 57)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Recipients: Klepacky, Amy B., 1993-1996 (Box 66, Folder 58)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Recipients: Lee, Richard B., 1993-1996 (Box 66, Folder 59)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Recipients: Montalbano, Andrew M., 1992-1996 (Box 66, Folder 60)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Recipients: Sephus, Erika E., 1993-1996 (Box 66, Folder 61)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Recipients: Smolder, Craig P., 1993-1996 (Box 66, Folder 62)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Alternates and Confirmations, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Recipients: Walpern-Argentina, 1994-1997 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Recipients: Butler-Bermuda, 1994-1995 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Recipients: Pedro dos Santas-Brazil, 1994-1996 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Recipients: Mejia-Costa Rica, 1994-1997 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Recipients: Toussaint-Dominica, 1994-1997 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Recipients: Magana-El Salvador, 1994-1997 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Recipients: Escobar-Guatemala, 1994-1997 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Recipients: Lagos-Ramos-Honduras, 1994-1997 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Alternates and District Confirmations, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Recipients: Baker, Christy L., 1994-1995 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Recipients: Green, G. Bradley, 1994-1995 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Recipients: Gunderson, Rebecca E., 1994-1995 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Recipients: Lotspeich, Walter B., 1994-1997 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Recipients: Morengo, Jaime L., 1994-1997 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Recipients: Needham, Kimberly A., 1994-1997 (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Recipients: O'Fare, Jollen D., 1994-1997 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Recipients: Ramussen, Andrew M., 1994-1997 (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Alternates and Confirmations, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Recipients: Ali-Argentina, 1995-1998 (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Recipients: Brizuela-Argentina, 1995-1998 (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Recipients: Boriollo-Brazil, 1995-1998 (Box 67, Folder 22)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Recipients: De Azevedo-Melo-Brazil, 1995-1998 (Box 67, Folder 23)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Recipients: Vergara-Martinez-Colombia, 1995-1998 (Box 67, Folder 24)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Recipients: Oviedo-Gomez-Costa Rica, 1995-1996 (Box 67, Folder 25)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Recipients: Coto-Vegaj-Panama, 1995-1999 (Box 67, Folder 26)
    - RHSF: Foreign Scholarships-Recipients: Pawirodjojo-Surinam, 1995-1999 (Box 67, Folder 27)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Alternates and District Confirmations, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 28)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Recipients: Brazzel, Lara A., 1995-1998 (Box 67, Folder 29)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Recipients: Chlebowski, Kimberly M., 1995-1998 (Box 67, Folder 30)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Recipients: Dicker, Bryan T., 1995-1998 (Box 67, Folder 31)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Recipients: Hinson, Christopher L., 1995-1996 (Box 67, Folder 32)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Recipients: Knollenberg, Lisa L., 1995-1999 (Box 67, Folder 33)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Recipients: Lovrin, Melanie C., 1995-1998 (Box 67, Folder 34)
    - RHSF: US Scholarships-Recipients: Mumm, Joshua J., 1995-1998 (Box 67, Folder 35)
  - Subseries I:E: Membership Files and Staff Activity Reports, 1980-1988.
    - Membership: AT&T Communications (ATTCOM)-Dues Rebates, Jan 1987-Jun 1987 (Box 67, Folder 36)
    - Membership: ATTCOM -Dues Rebates, Jul 1987-Dec 1987 (Box 67, Folder 37)
    - Membership: ATTCOM-01, 1998 (Box 67, Folder 38)
    - Membership: ATTCOM MMS-MLO-01, 1988 (Box 67, Folder 39)
    - Membership: ATTCOM-02, 1988 (Box 67, Folder 40)
    - Membership: ATTCOM-03, Jan 1988-Apr 1988 (Box 67, Folder 41)
    - Membership: ATTCOM-03, May 1988-Nov 1988 (Box 67, Folder 42)
    - Membership: ATTCOM-04, 1988 (Box 67, Folder 43)
    - Membership: ATTCOM-05, Jan 1988-Mar 1988 (Box 67, Folder 44)
    - Membership: ATTCOM-05, Apr 1988-Aug 1988 (Box 67, Folder 45)
    - Membership: AT&T Information Systems (ATTIS)-01, 1987 (Box 67, Folder 46)
    - Membership: ATTIS-02, Jan 1987-Apr 1987 (Box 67, Folder 47)
    - Membership: ATTIS-02, May 1987-Dec 1987 (Box 67, Folder 48)
    - Membership: ATTIS-03, Jan 1987-Apr 1987 (Box 67, Folder 49)
    - Membership: ATTIS-03, May 1987-Dec 1987 (Box 67, Folder 50)
    - Membership: ATTIS-05, 1987 (Box 67, Folder 51)
    - Membership: ATTIS-06, 1987 (Box 67, Folder 52)
    - Membership: ATTIS-07, 1987 (Box 67, Folder 53)
    - Membership: District 7, 1988 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Membership: District 9, 1988 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Membership: District 13, 1988 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Membership: Dues, Jan 1988 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Membership: Dues, Feb 1988 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Membership: Dues, Mar 1988 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Membership: Dues, Apr 1988 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Membership: Dues, May 1988 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Membership: Dues, Jun 1988 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Membership: Dues, Jul 1988 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Membership: Dues, Aug 1988 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Membership: Dues Deduction Authorization, Applications, 1988 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Membership: Dues Deduction Authorization, Company, 1988 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Membership: H-166 Membership Dues Report, 1988 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Membership: Local Bank Account, 1988 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Membership: Local Refund, 1988 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Membership: Office and Professional Employees International Union, 19888 (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 1-Allen, Clara L., 1985-1986 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 1-Ash, Michael P., 1985-1986 (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 1-Bahr, Morton, 1985 (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 1-Baxter, Edward, 1986 (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 1-Chernoff, Mark, 1985-1986 (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 1-Cohen, Larry, 1985-1986 (Box 68, Folder 23)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 1-Dennis, J.H., Jr., 1985-1986 (Box 68, Folder 24)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 1-Dolan, Donna J., 1985-1986 (Box 68, Folder 25)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 1- Gallant, Ellen, 1986 (Box 68, Folder 26)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 1-Gay-Fantani, Carol E., 1985-1986 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 1-Grieco, Michael L., 1985-1986 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 1-Hayes, Jeremiah J., 1985-1986 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 1-Hook, Donald C., 1986 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 1-Hoffman, Anna F., 1985-1986 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 1-Kaufman, Alan, 1985-1986 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 1-Keefe, John, 1985-1986 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 1-King, Kathleen A., 1985-1986 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 1-Kirlin, Eileen, 1985 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 1-Lewis, Richard, 1985-1986 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 1-Loos, John, 1985-1986 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 1-Mancino, Lawrence, 1985-1986 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 1-McKelligan, William J., 1985-1986 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 1-Money, Calvin W., 1985-1986 (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 1-Niven, Pat, 1985-1986 (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 1-O'Brien, John J., 1985-1986 (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 1-Pierce, Jan D., 1985-1986 (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 1-Pursell, Robert, 1985-1986 (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 1-Rosenthal, Steve, 1985-1986 (Box 69, Folder 19)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 1-Sanchez, Don M., 1981-1982 (Box 69, Folder 20)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 1-Sanchez, Don M., 1983-1984 (Box 69, Folder 21)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 1-Siano, Michael J., 1985-1986 (Box 69, Folder 22)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 1-Taylor, Adrienne R., 1985-1986 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 1-Thompson, Willie, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 1-Trivelli, Vince, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 1-Turchi, Carmine, 1985-1986 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 1-Wallace, Patricia J., 1986 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 1-Watkins, Ted J., 1985 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 1-Williams, Gloria, 1985 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 1-Woods, Ronald E., 1985-1986 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 2-Angel, Charles, 1980-1981 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 2-Angel, Charles, 1985-1986 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 2-Belanger, Gerard, 1985-1986 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 2-Bickers, J. William, 1985-1986 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 2-Catucci, Peter G., 1986 (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 2-Dinkins, Jim, 1980-1981 (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 2-Dinkins, Jim, 1985-1986 (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 2-Dotson, Jack R., 1980-1981 (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 2-Dotson, Jack R., 1985-1986 (Box 70, Folder 17)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 2-Leonard, Grace, 1980-1981 (Box 70, Folder 18)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 2-Leonard, Grace, 1985-1986 (Box 70, Folder 19)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 2-Lephardt, Barbara J., 1985-1986 (Box 70, Folder 20)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 2-Lewinski, Edwin, 1980-1981 (Box 70, Folder 21)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 2-Lewinski, Edwin, 1985-1986 (Box 70, Folder 22)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 2-Linder, Michael L., 1980-1981 (Box 70, Folder 23)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 2-Linder, Michael L., 1985-1986 (Box 70, Folder 24)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 2-Mazzi, James E., 1980-1981 (Box 70, Folder 25)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 2-Mazzi, James E., 1985-1986 (Box 70, Folder 26)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 2-O'Connell, John E. Jr., 1980-1981 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 2-O'Hara, Mary C., 1980-1981 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 2-Sangmeister, Charles J., 1980-1981 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 2-Sangmeister, Charles J., 1985-1986 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 2-Schutz, Edward A., 1985-1986 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 2-Strick, George R., 1980-1981 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 2 and 24-Strick, George R., 1985-1986 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Adler, James D., 1980-1981 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Adler, James D., 1985-1986 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3 and 10-Baccari, Jack, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Bragg, Rita M., 1981-1982 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Bragg, Rita M., 1983-1985 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3 and 10-Bryant, Mary I., 1986 (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3 and 10-Burch, Selina, 1980-1981 (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Collins, Walter F., 1985-1986 (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3 and 10-Dearing, Dennis, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3 and 10-Deroven, Leroy, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Earley, John J., 1980-1981 (Box 71, Folder 18)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Earley, John J., 1985-1986 (Box 71, Folder 19)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Finn, D.C.H., Jr., 1980-1981 (Box 71, Folder 20)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Flint, Avery, 1980-1981 (Box 71, Folder 21)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Flint, Avery, 1985-1986 (Box 71, Folder 22)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Gordon, Delbert, 1980-1981 (Box 71, Folder 23)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Harper, E.L. "Jim", 1980-1981 (Box 71, Folder 24)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Head, H.E. "Gene", 1980-1981 (Box 71, Folder 25)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Head, H.E. "Gene", 1985-1986 (Box 71, Folder 26)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Holder, J.W., 1980-1981 (Box 71, Folder 27)
    - Staff Activity Reports: Horlander, Nelle P., 1986 (Box 71, Folder 28)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3 and 10-Johnson, Wallace E., 1986 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Mincey, Harold B., 1985-1986 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Moran, Francis L., 1985-1986 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Morgan, P.J., 1980-1981 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Moudy, Martha M., 1980-1981 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Moudy, Martha, 1985-1986 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3 and 10-Patrick, Calvin, 1986 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Philips, James F., 1980-1981 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Philips, James F., 1985-1986 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Porch, R.B., 1980-1981 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3- Porch, R.B., 1985-1986 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3 and 10-Powell, George E., 1986 (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3 and 10-Powell, Norma C., 1986 (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3 and 10-Powell, R. Stanley, 1986 (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Pribank, Mark, 1980-1981 (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Russo, Gene, 1980-1981 (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Russo, Gene, 1985-1986 (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Ruth, Kenneth S., 1985-1986 (Box 72, Folder 18)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Ryles, Tim, 1985-1986 (Box 72, Folder 19)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Scares, John W., 1985-1986 (Box 72, Folder 20)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Seawall, Edward D., 1980-1981 (Box 72, Folder 21)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Shehan, Carol, 1980-1981 (Box 72, Folder 22)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Smith, James E., Jr., 1980-1981 (Box 72, Folder 23)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Smith, James E., Jr., 1985-1986 (Box 72, Folder 24)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Stanford, Selina, 1985-1986 (Box 72, Folder 25)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3 and 10-Stearman, Doug, 1986 (Box 72, Folder 26)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3 and 10-Swain, Harry E., 1986 (Box 72, Folder 27)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Vaughn, Nola R., 1986 (Box 72, Folder 28)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Walker, John V., 1980-1981 (Box 72, Folder 29)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Walker, John V., 1985-1986 (Box 72, Folder 30)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Walraven/Noles, Nettie, 1980-1981 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Walraven, Nettie, 1985-1986 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Warren, Pat A., 1980-1981 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Warren, Pat A., 1985-1986 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Willis, Allen D., Jr., 1980-1981 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Willis, Allen D., Jr., 1985-1986 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 3-Zwackis, John S., 1986 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 4-Anderson, Florine B., 1980-1981 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 4-Anderson, Florine B., 1985-1986 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 4-Andrietsch, Joseph F., 1986 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 4-Cantrell, Grover, 1986 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 4 and 5-Craig, Sharon A., 1985-1986 (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 4 and 5-Davenport, Ronald E., 1986 (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 4-Derrig, David, 1986 (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 4-Diekman, Thomas A., 1980-1981 (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 4 and 18-Diekman, Thomas A., 1985-1986 (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 4 and 5-Disch, Edward A., 1986 (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 4-Echlin, Charles E., 1980-1981 (Box 73, Folder 18)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 4-Echlin, Charles E., 1985-1986 (Box 73, Folder 19)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 4-Handley, Michael I., 1980-1981 (Box 73, Folder 20)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 4-Handley, Michael I., 1985-1986 (Box 73, Folder 21)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 4-Higenbottom, Marie, 1980-1981 (Box 73, Folder 22)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 4-Higenbottom, Marie, 1985-1986 (Box 73, Folder 23)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 4-Hughes, Martin J., 1980-1981 (Box 73, Folder 24)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 4-Hughes, Martin J., 1985-1986 (Box 73, Folder 25)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 4-Johnson, Robert D., 1980-1981 (Box 73, Folder 26)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 4-Johnson, Robert D., 1985-1986 (Box 73, Folder 27)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 4 and 5-Joyce, Michael N., 1986 (Box 73, Folder 28)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 4-Lindemier, Donald H., 1980-1981 (Box 73, Folder 29)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 4-Lindmier, Donald H., 1985-1986 (Box 73, Folder 30)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 4 and 5-Martin, Gwendolyn R., 1986 (Box 73, Folder 31)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 4 and 5-Modjeski, Julian A., 1986 (Box 73, Folder 32)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 4 and 5-Moran, Daniel J., 1986 (Box 73, Folder 33)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 4-Rechenbach, Jeffery A., 1981 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 4-Rechenbach, Jeffery A., 1985-1986 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 4-Scates, John S., 1980-1981 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Staff Activity Reports: District 4-Seifert, Adrian C., 1981 (Box 74, Folder 4)